[
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy",
    "subject": "Previous Qs2",
    "systems": "Upper limb7",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles2",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor carpi radialis",
    "Answer2": "Palmaris longus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor digitorum superficialis ",
    "Answer4": "Flexor carpi ulnaris",
    "Answer5": "Flexor pollicis longus ",
    "Answer6": "Flexor pollicis longus DLKSDF",
    "Answer": "Flexor digitorum superficialis ",
    "questiontext": "All the following muscles are supplied by median nerve or its branches except?",
    "explanation": " Nodsflsdfslkjfs"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy",
    "subject": "Previous Qs3",
    "systems": "Upper limb3",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles3",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer2": "Palmaris longus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor digitorum superficialis ",
    "Answer4": "Medial part of flexor digitorum profundus",
    "Answer5": "Flexor pollicis longus ",
    "Answer": "Flexor pollicis longus ",
    "questiontext": "All the following muscles are supplied by median nerve or its branches except ?"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor carpi radialis",
    "Answer2": "Palmaris longus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor digitorum superficialis ",
    "Answer4": "Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer5": "Flexor digitorum Profundus",
    "Answer6": "Flexor pollicis longus DLKSDF",
    "Answer": "Flexor digitorum Profundus",
    "questiontext": "All the following have attachment with Common flexor origin except?",
    "explanation": "One of tg pair havSDFLK"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor digitorum Profundus",
    "Answer2": "Flexor Pollicis longus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor digitorum superficialis ",
    "Answer4": "Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer5": "Flexor carpi ulnaris",
    "Answer": "Flexor digitorum superficialis ",
    "questiontext": "All the following muscles cross the wrist joint except    ?  ",
    "explanation": "One of tg pair havSDFLK"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor pollicis longus and Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer2": "Flexor digitorum Profundus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor digitorum superficialis and palmaris longus",
    "Answer4": "Flexor pollicis longus and Flexor digitorum profundus",
    "Answer5": "Flexor digitorum profundus and flexor carpi ulnaris",
    "Answer": "Flexor digitorum Profundus",
    "questiontext": "One of the following pair have origin from interosseous membrane  ?"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor Pollicis longus",
    "Answer2": "flexor carpi ulnaris",
    "Answer3": "Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer4": "Flexor carpi radialis",
    "Answer5": "Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer6": "Flexor Dicis longus",
    "Answer": "Flexor Dicis longus",
    "questiontext": "All the following consider within superficial group of forearm except?"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor digitorum Profundus and Flexor pollicis longus",
    "Answer2": "Pronator quadratus and Flexor digitorum Profundus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor pollicis longus and Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer4": "Flexor digitorum Superficialis and Flexor Pollicis longus",
    "Answer5": "None of the above",
    "Answer": "Flexor pollicis longus and Pronator quadratus",
    "questiontext": "One of the following pairs have origin from Ulna ?",
    "explanation": "One of tg pair havSDFLK"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor pollicis longus and Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer2": "Flexor carpi radialis and palmaris longus",
    "Answer3": "Flexor carpi Ulnaris and medial part of flexor digitorum superficialis",
    "Answer4": "Flexor carpi Ulnaris and medial part of flexor digitorum profundus",
    "Answer5": "None of the above",
    "Answer": "Flexor pollicis longus and Pronator quadratus",
    "questiontext": "One of following pair have nerve supply from ulnar nerve           ?   "
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Pronator teres",
    "Answer2": "Flexor digitorum superficialis",
    "Answer3": "Flexor digitorum profundus",
    "Answer4": "Pronator quadratus",
    "Answer5": "Flexor pollicis longus",
    "Answer": "Pronator quadratus",
    "questiontext": "All the following have origin from the ulna except          ? ",
    "explanation": "One of tg pair havSDFLK"
  },
  {
    "courses": "Anatomy mid",
    "subject": "Previous Qs",
    "systems": "Upper limb",
    "topic": "Anterior compartment muscles",
    "totalPoint": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flexor digitorum profundus --- Inserted at bases of distal phalanges of medial 4 fingers",
    "Answer2": "Flexor digitorum superficialis---Inserted at Middle phalanx of medial four fingers",
    "Answer3": "Flexor Pollicis longus ----- Inserted at base of middle phalanx of thumb",
    "Answer4": "Flexor carpi ulnaris ----Inserted at Pisiform, pisohamate ligament and pisometacarpal ligament ",
    "Answer5": "None of the above",
    "Answer6": "QuadrDSSDFnt extends between the neck of the radius and above the radial noDSa",
    "Answer": "QuadrDSSDFnt extends between the neck of the radius and above the radial noDSa",
    "questiontext": "All the following matches are true except        ? "
  }

]
